<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<chapter xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook ../../lib/docbook-5/xsd/docbook.xsd" xml:id="concern">
	<title>Concern</title>
	<para>
		Concerns are the distinctive building blocks of a Compose* application, in addition to the building blocks of
		the base language. Conceptually concerns are an extension to classes. Concerns are declared in files with a
		<emphasis>.cps</emphasis>
		extension.
	</para>
	<para>
		A concern has three different parts: zero or more filter modules, an optional superimposition part, and an
		optional implementation part. The filter modules are superimposed on classes by the filter module binding field
		of the superimposition. The implementation part contains language dependent code of the concern.
	</para>
	<section xml:id="concern.syntax">
		<title>Syntax</title>
		<figure xml:id="concern.grammar">
			<title>Concern syntax</title>
			<programlisting language="EBNF"><![CDATA[Concern = 'concern' Identifier [ConcernParameters] ['in' Namespace] ConcernBlock;
ConcernParameters = '(' Identifier ':' Type {',' Identifier ':' Type } ')';
Type = Fqn;
Fqn = Identifier {'.' Identifier};
Namespace = Fqn;
ConcernBlock = '{' {FilterModule} [SuperImposition] [Implementation] '}';
]]></programlisting>
			<remark role="todo">This needs to be converted to a productionset</remark>
		</figure>
		<para>
			The syntax for a concern definition is shown in
			<xref xlink:href="#concern.grammar" />
			. A concern name must be unique for the namespace where it is declared. It often has the same name as the
			<emphasis>.cps</emphasis>
			file in which it is declared, but this is not a requirement. It is not possible to place two concerns in one
			file. The ordering of the filter modules, superimposition, and implementation is fixed.
		</para>
	</section>
	<section xml:id="concern.semantics">
		<title>Semantics</title>
		<para>
			The concern is the main language entity of Compose*, it consists of one or more filter modules, an optional
			superimposition part, and an optional implementation part. How these are combined depends on how you use a
			Compose* concern. There are two different types of usage of a concern. We will look here to the usage that
			comes from the conceptual idea, which assumes that a class is a concern. This means that every class can be
			written as a concern, with an implementation part and one or more filter modules. To superimpose these
			concerns onto other classes, a concern is used with a superimposition part; this concern can be seen as a
			sort of aspect specification.
		</para>
	</section>
	<section xml:id="concern.examples">
		<title>Examples</title>
		<example xml:id="concern.concerntemplate">
			<title>Abstract example of a concern</title>
			<programlisting language="composestar"><![CDATA[concern aConcern in aNamespace {
  filtermodule A {
    ...
  }
  
  filtermodule B {
    ...
  }
  
  superimposition {
    ...
  }
  
  implementation {
    ...
  }
}]]></programlisting>
		</example>
		<para>
			A concern heading consists of a concern name, optional concern parameters, and an optional namespace
			declaration. If no namespace is specified, the concern is located in the root of a project. The namespace
			has identical semantics as namespaces in other languages (like Java and C#).
		</para>
		<para>
			In the concern it is possible to define one or more filter modules, one superimposition block, and an
			implementation part. A possible concern is demonstrated in
			<xref xlink:href="#concern.concerntemplate" />
			.
		</para>
	</section>
	<section>
		<title>Legality Rules</title>
		<itemizedlist>
			<listitem>
				<simpara>The identifier of a concern must be unique for the namespace where it is declared in</simpara>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<simpara>The ordering of filter modules, superimposition, and implementation is fixed</simpara>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<simpara>There can be maximal one superimposition and implementation part</simpara>
			</listitem>
		</itemizedlist>
	</section>

	<!-- <xi:include href="concern-comments.xml" />  -->

	<section>
		<title>Further Reading</title>
		<para>
			In the comments section of this chapter
			<biblioref linkend="bergmans.aosdbook05" />
			is already mentioned, this is a good source for the theory behind concerns.
		</para>
	</section>

</chapter>
